[
    {
        "enPrompt": "Write DFS algorithm for the given graph",
        "arPrompt": "اكتب خوارزمية البحث بالعمق للبيان المعطى",
        "cAnswer": "Source/GraphAlgorithms/dfs.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/GraphAlgorithms/dfs.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/GraphAlgorithms/dfs.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/GraphAlgorithms/dfs.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Find and return the minimum in the given array `a`",
        "arPrompt": "جد و أرجع أصغر عدد في المصفوفة المعطاة م",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/min_in_array.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/min_in_array.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/min_in_array.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/min_in_array.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Find and return the maximum in the given array `a`",
        "arPrompt": "جد و أرجع أكبر عدد في المصفوفة المعطاة م",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/max_in_array.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/max_in_array.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/max_in_array.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/max_in_array.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Invert the given string `s` and return the result",
        "arPrompt": "اعكس السلسلة النصية المعطاة س و أرجع النتيجة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/invert_string.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/invert_string.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/invert_string.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/invert_string.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Invert the given array `a` and return the result",
        "arPrompt": "اعكس المصفوفة المعطاة م و أرجع النتيجة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/invert_array.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/invert_array.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/invert_array.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/invert_array.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Find and return the sum of the given array `a`",
        "arPrompt": "جد و أرجع ناتج جمع عناصر المصفوفة المعطاة م",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/sum_array.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/sum_array.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/sum_array.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/sum_array.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "apply the given function `f` on each element of the given array `a` and return the result",
        "arPrompt": "طبق الدالة المعطاة د على كل عنصر من عناصر المصفوفة المعطاة م و أرجع النتيجة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/for_each.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/for_each.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/for_each.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/for_each.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "reduce the given array `a` using the given function `f` and return the result",
        "arPrompt": "اختصر المصفوفة المعطاة م باستعمال الدالة المعطاة د و أرجع النتيجة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/reduce.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/reduce.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/reduce.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/reduce.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "accumulate the given array `a` using the given function `f` and keep the partial results and return them",
        "arPrompt": "راكم المصفوفة المعطاة م باستعمال الدالة المعطاة د و احتفط بكل النتائج الجزئية و أرجعهم",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/accumulate.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/accumulate.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/accumulate.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/accumulate.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "extract unique elements in the given array and return the result",
        "arPrompt": "استخرج العناصر الفريدة من المصفوفة المعطاة و أرجع النتيجة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/unique.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/unique.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/unique.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/unique.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "filter the given array based on the given function `f` and return the result",
        "arPrompt": "قم بتصفية المصفوفة المعطاة بناءً على الدالة المعطاة د و أرجع النتيجة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/filter.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/filter.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/filter.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/filter.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "calculate and return the mean of the given array",
        "arPrompt": "احسب و أرجع المتوسط الحسابي للمصفوفة المعطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/mean.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/mean.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/mean.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/mean.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "calculate and return the standard deviation of the given array",
        "arPrompt": "احسب الانحراف المعياري للمصفوفة المعطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/std.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/std.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/std.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/std.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "print the given array",
        "arPrompt": "اطبع المصفوفة المعطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/print.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/print.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/print.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/print.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "rotate the given array counterclockwise and return the result",
        "arPrompt": "دور المصفوفة المعطاة بعكس اتجاه عقارب الساعة و أرجع النتيجة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/rotate.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/rotate.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/rotate.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/rotate.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "calculate and return the sum of the given array in a given range",
        "arPrompt": "احسب و أرجع مجموع عناصر مصفوفة معطاة في مجال معطى",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/sum_range_array.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/sum_range_array.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/sum_range_array.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/sum_range_array.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Find and return the position of a given element in the given array starting from its end",
        "arPrompt": "جد و أرجع موقع عنصر معطى في مصفوفة معطاة بدءاً من نهايتها",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/rfind.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/rfind.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/rfind.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/rfind.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Insert an element at a given position in the given array",
        "arPrompt": "احشر عنصرا في موقع معطى ضمن المصفوفة المعطى",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/insert.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/insert.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/insert.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/insert.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Delete an element at a given position in the given array",
        "arPrompt": "احذف عنصرا من موقع معطى ضمن المصفوفة المعطى",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/erase.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/erase.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/erase.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/erase.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Write Floyd Warshall algorithm for a given graph",
        "arPrompt": "اكتب خوارزمية Floyd Warshall لبيان معطى",
        "cAnswer": "Source/GraphAlgorithms/floyd_warshall.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/GraphAlgorithms/floyd_warshall.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/GraphAlgorithms/floyd_warshall.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/GraphAlgorithms/floyd_warshall.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "check if a given character is from the alphabet",
        "arPrompt": "اختبر فيما إذا كان محرف معطى من الأبجدية",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/is_alpha.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/is_alpha.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/is_alpha.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/is_alpha.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "check if a given character is a digit",
        "arPrompt": "اختبر فيما إذا كان المحرف المعطى رقما بين 0 و 9",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/is_digit.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/is_digit.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/is_digit.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/is_digit.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "check if all characters of a given string are alphanumeric",
        "arPrompt": "اختبر فيما إذا كانت كل محارف سلسلة نصية معطاة من الأبجدية أو الأرقام",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/is_string_alphanumeric.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/is_string_alphanumeric.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/is_string_alphanumeric.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/is_string_alphanumeric.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "check if a given string contains a given char",
        "arPrompt": "اختبر فيما إذا كانت سلسلة نصية معطاة تحتوي محرفا معطى",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/char_exists.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/char_exists.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/char_exists.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/char_exists.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "check if a given array contains a given element",
        "arPrompt": "اختبر فيما إذا كانت مصفوفة معطاة تحتوي على عنصر معطى",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/exists.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/exists.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/exists.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/exists.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "find and return the position of a given char in a given string",
        "arPrompt": "جد و أرجع موقع محرف معطى ضمن سلسلة نصية معطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/find_char.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/find_char.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/find_char.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/find_char.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "find and return the position of a given char in a given string starting from its end",
        "arPrompt": "جد و أرجع موقع محرف معطى ضمن سلسلة نصية معطاة بدءاً من نهايتها",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/rfind_char.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/rfind_char.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/rfind_char.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/rfind_char.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "calculate and return the area of a traingle from its points",
        "arPrompt": "احسب و أرجع مساحة مثلت من إحداثيات نقاطه",
        "cAnswer": "Source/Geometry/traingle_area.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/Geometry/traingle_area.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/Geometry/triangle_area.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/Geometry/triangle_area.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "calculate and return the area of polygon given its vertices",
        "arPrompt": "احسب و أرجع مساحة مضلع من إحداثيات رؤوسه",
        "cAnswer": "Source/Geometry/polygon_area.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/Geometry/polygon_area.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/Geometry/polygon_area.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/Geometry/polygon_area.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "check if three given points are collinear",
        "arPrompt": "اختبر فيما إذا كانت 3 نقاط معطاة على استقامة واحدة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/Geometry/are_collinear.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/Geometry/are_collinear.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/Geometry/are_collinear.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/Geometry/are_collinear.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "convert string to lowercase and return the result",
        "arPrompt": "حول حالة محارف سلسلة نصية إلى أحرف صغيرة و أرجع النتيجة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/to_lower.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/to_lower.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/to_lower.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/to_lower.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "convert string to uppercase and return the result",
        "arPrompt": "حول حالة محارف سلسلة نصية إلى أحرف كبيرة و أرجع النتيجة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/to_upper.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/to_upper.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/to_upper.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/to_upper.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "write the insertion sort algorithm for a given array",
        "arPrompt": "اكتب خوارزمية الفرز بالحشر لمصفوفة معطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/Sorting/insertion_sort.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/Sorting/insertion_sort.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/Sorting/insertion_sort.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/Sorting/insertion_sort.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "write the selection sort algorithm for a given array",
        "arPrompt": "اكتب خوارزمية الفرز بالاختيار لمصفوفة معطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/Sorting/selection_sort.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/Sorting/selection_sort.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/Sorting/selection_sort.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/Sorting/selection_sort.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "write the counting sort algorithm for a given array",
        "arPrompt": "اكتب خوارزمية الفرز بالعد لمصفوفة معطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/Sorting/counting_sort.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/Sorting/counting_sort.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/Sorting/counting_sort.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/Sorting/counting_sort.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "write the merge sort algorithm for a given array",
        "arPrompt": "اكتب خوارزمية الفرز بالدمج لمصفوفة معطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/Sorting/merge_sort.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/Sorting/merge_sort.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/Sorting/merge_sort.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/Sorting/merge_sort.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "find  and return the farthest point to a given point from a given set of points",
        "arPrompt": "جد و أرجع أبعد نقطة من بين مجموعة من النقاط المعطاة عن نقطة معطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/Geometry/farthest_point.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/Geometry/farthest_point.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/Geometry/farthest_point.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/Geometry/farthest_point.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "find and return the closest point to a given point from a given set of points",
        "arPrompt": "جد و أرجع أقرب نقطة من بين مجموعة من النقاط المعطاة عن نقطة معطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/Geometry/closest_point.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/Geometry/closest_point.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/Geometry/closest_point.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/Geometry/closest_point.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "calculate and return the frequency of each element in the given array",
        "arPrompt": "احسب و أرجع تكرار كل عنصر في المصفوفة المعطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/frequency.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/frequency.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/frequency.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/frequency.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "find and return the most frequent item in a given array",
        "arPrompt": "جد و أرجع أكثر عنصر مكرر في المصفوفة المعطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/find_most_frequent.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/find_most_frequent.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/find_most_frequent.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/find_most_frequent.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "check if a given string starts with another given string",
        "arPrompt": "تحقق فيما إذا كانت سلسلة نصية معطاة تبدأ بسلسلة نصية أخرى معطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/starts_with.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/starts_with.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/starts_with.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/starts_with.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "check if a given string ends with another given string",
        "arPrompt": "تحقق فيما إذا كانت سلسلة نصية معطاة تنتهي بسلسلة نصية أخرى معطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/ends_with.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/ends_with.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/ends_with.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/ends_with.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Remove any whitespace character from both ends of a given string",
        "arPrompt": "أزل أي محرف فراغ من كلتا نهايتي سلسلة نصية معطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Find the first index at which the two given arrays differ, return -1 if not found",
        "arPrompt": "جد أول دليل تختلف عنده المصفوفتان المعطاتان، ارجع -1 إذا لم يوجد هكذا دليل",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/find_diff_index.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/find_diff_index.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/find_diff_index.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/find_diff_index.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Slice a given array within a given range",
        "arPrompt": "اجتزئ مصفوفة معطاة ضمن مجال معطى",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/array_slice.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/array_slice.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/array_slice.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/array_slice.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Slice a given string within a given range and return the result",
        "arPrompt": "اجتزئ سلسلة نصية معطاة ضمن مجال معطى و ارجع النتيجة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/string_slice.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/string_slice.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/string_slice.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/string_slice.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Replace a given char with another given char in a given string and return the new string",
        "arPrompt": "استبدل محرف معطى بآخر معطى في سلسلة نصية معطاة و ارجع السلسلة النصية الجديدة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/replace.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/replace.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/replace.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/replace.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Replace a given value with another given value in a given array",
        "arPrompt": "استبدل قيمة معطاة بآخرى معطاة في مصفوفة معطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/replace.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/replace.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/replace.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/replace.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Check if a given array is ordered and return 1 in case of Ascending order, -1 in case of Descending order, 0 otherwise",
        "arPrompt": "تحقق فيما إذا كانت مصفوفة معطاة مرتبة و ارجع 1 في حال كانت مرتبة تصاعديًا، -1 في حال كانت مرتبة تنازليًا، 0 في حال كانت غير مرتبة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/check_order.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/check_order.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/check_order.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/check_order.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Clip the values of a given array within a given range",
        "arPrompt": "اقتطع قيم مصفوفة معطاة ضمن مجال معطى",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/clip.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/clip.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/clip.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/clip.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Initialize a given array with a given size by a given value",
        "arPrompt": "هيئ مصفوفة معطاة لها حجم معطى بقيمة معطاة",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/init_array.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/init_array.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/init_array.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/init_array.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Split a given string into a list of strings based on a given character",
        "arPrompt": "جزئ نص معطى إلى لائحة من النصوص بناء على محرف معطى",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/split.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/split.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/split.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/split.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Check if all elements in a given array satisfy a criteria defined by a function with boolean return value",
        "arPrompt": "تفحص فيما إذا كان كل عناصر مصفوفة معطاة تحقق معيار معرف بدالة تعيد قيمة ثـنائية",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/check_all.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/check_all.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/check_all.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/check_all.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "Check if any element in a given array satisfy a criteria defined by a function with boolean return value",
        "arPrompt": "تفحص فيما إذا كان أي عنصر في مصفوفة معطاة يحقق معيار معرف بدالة تعيد قيمة ثـنائية",
        "cAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/check_any.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/check_any.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/check_any.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/ArrayRelatedOperations/check_any.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    },
    {
        "enPrompt": "",
        "arPrompt": "",
        "cAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.c",
        "jsAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.js",
        "enAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.en.alusus",
        "arAlususAnswer": "Source/StringRelatedOperations/trim.ar.alusus"
    }
]
